I think AI scratches a human itch but doesn't fully satisfy, instead of having real friendships
we have social media. And so it's these diet coke versions of what we actually want.
And so I think there's going to be a barbell experience of everything is truly fake and on
the other side people want super real. So there's tons of gen alphas and gen zers who are like
switching back to flip phones because they're like they want to disconnect to this. There's
people who are like the demand for ranches and moving out in the middle of nowhere has gone up.
And so I think there's a percentage of people that are rejecting it or rejecting for a portion
of their lives and there are people leaning into it. I think reality will probably be a
blend of these two extremes. I think the middle is where businesses will suffer.
Like you have to know which game you're playing.